Then I'll go first
那我先
Then I'll go back to work first
那我先回去工作了
For my new job, I have to
新的工作我得
Get familiar with it quickly
赶快熟悉起来
Come to my house today after work
下班后今天来我家吧
Have dinner together
一起吃个饭
I
我
I have to go home to dinner with my mother
得回家陪我妈妈吃饭
Then you plan to go on
那你就打算以后
Just run back and forth at both ends
就这么来回两头跑啊
The situation in my family
我家的情况
My mother, she can't live alone
我妈妈 她不能单独住
So this is it
那这样
You get off work early today
今天你早点下班
Go with your mother first
先去陪你妈
Then come to my house again
然后再来我家
Eat supper
吃夜宵
I'm going to work first
我先去上班了
Anjie
安捷
The marketing department
市场部那边
Are you looking for
是不是想找
A new spokesman
新的代言人
Yeah
对啊
Enter the preparation period for listing
进入上市准备期
There must be promotion work
得有推广工作
Divine mystery
神神秘秘
Don't consult with us
不和我们商量
It has a problem with us
是对我们有意见啊
Let's go
走吧
Before Mr. Su entered the office,
苏总进办公室前
Dress as if
穿的好像
It's not this dress, is it
不是这身衣服吧
Good good
好 好 好
It can be no problem
可以没问题
Before Mr. Yu entered the office,
余总进办公室前
I'm not wearing it either
穿的也不是
This dress
这身衣服吧
I don't know
我不知道
Mr. Wang
王总
Do you want to find the public relations department for the plan
方案要不要找公关部
Check it
对一下
Why don't you submit an application
要不你提交个申请
Also transferred to the public relations department
也调到公关部去
Public Relations Department
公关部
They are all Su Kelan's people
都是苏可岚的人
If this story comes to light
这件事情要是传到
Inside her ears
她的耳朵里边
Accurate bad things
准得坏事
You still talk to the other company
你们还是跟对方公司
Direct communication
直接沟通
Good
好
OK
好的
Why is he so scared
他怎么那么怕
Sue always knows bad things will happen
苏总知道会坏事
Yu Zong and Su Zong
余总和苏总
What's the relationship now
现在什么关系
Everyone with a discerning eye knows
明眼人都知道
If you're the boss's girlfriend
你要是老板女朋友
Can you agree to this plan
这方案你能同意吗
Hello
喂
How about this one? Does it look good
怎么样 这件好不好看
Not on the phone
电话里不说
Are you going to die
你要死了吗
Right
对呀
I'm so happy that I'm dying
我开心得都要死了
Yu Han told me
雨涵和我说
Yu Hao is talking to our company
余昊在跟我们公司
On the endorsement of "what to eat"
谈“吃什么”的代言
I'm going to rekindle my love with him
我要跟他重燃爱火啦
Are you nuts
你有病吧
I'm telling you
我告诉你啊
Next time, even if you really die,
下回就算你真死
Don't you call me either
你也别给我打电话
Don't go
别走嘛
When I help you transform your image,
我帮你改造形象的时候
How much effort did it take
费多大劲
I'm about to break my leg
我腿都要跑断了
Until you have to help me
到你要帮我
When I was a staff officer,
参谋的时候
That's your ghost attitude
你就是这种鬼态度啊
What kind of person are you
什么人啊你
Kindness turns on vendetta, you
恩将仇报啊你
What you changed has a ghost use
你改的有个鬼用
At least for now
那至少现在
Does your mother-in-law like you
丈母娘是喜欢你的吧
It's not time to give up yet
还没到放弃的时候
Refueling
加油
Quick, quick, quick
快 快 快
It's time to repay me
报答我的时候到了
How about taking a look at it for me
帮我看看怎么样嘛
My taste. When did you
我的品味你什么时候
It's eye-catching
看得上眼了
At least you are a man
好歹你也算个男人嘛
What
什么
I want to fight for Yu Hao
我要争取余昊
Of course you have to know men's
当然要知道男人的
Preferences
喜好
Take a look at it for me
帮我看看
Which looks good
哪个好看
Are you giving
你是给
Endorsement of the vegetable selling platform
卖菜平台代言的
The purpose is to make
目的是让
My sister likes to buy food
买菜姐姐喜欢
What you're wearing
你这身穿的
Seduce with
跟勾引
Buy food like a sister and husband
买菜姐姐老公似的
Sister grocery shopping
买菜姐姐
You'll be good if you don't smoke
不抽你就不错了
Yu Hao's brain smoked
余昊脑子抽了
I will ask you to speak for me
才会找你代言
How is it
怎么样
Professional suit
职业套装
Clear or not pure
清不清纯
Occupational or non-professional
职不职业
Why are you leaving again
你怎么又走啊
What's on your mind
你脑子里想什么呢
Yu Hao and Su Kelan
余昊和苏可岚
Already together
已经在一起了
Then together
那在一起
Can't we break up
就不能分手吗
Su Kelan and Yu Hao
苏可岚和余昊
We can't get together at all
根本就过不到一起去
Why
为什么
I heard that
我听说
They're not at all
他俩根本
I didn't live together
就没有住到一起去
Su Kelan's most important
苏可岚最重要的
What is it
是什么
Not Yu Hao
不是余昊
It's mom
是妈妈
Mom needs someone to take care of her
妈妈需要人照顾
So they can't be like
所以他们根本不能像
Living together like a normal couple
正常情侣一样同居
The most important thing in Yu Hao
那余昊最重要的
What is it
是什么呢
It's work
是工作
Not Su Kelan
不是苏可岚
Do you think they can make it
你说 他俩能成吗
Then Yu Hao likes to work so much
那余昊那么喜欢工作
Of course it is
那当然是
It's the best match for me
跟我最搭了
He works and I work
他工作我也工作
I can still speak for him
我还能帮他代言呢
Su Kelan
苏可岚嘛
What happened to Su Kelan
苏可岚怎么了
Of course, that's the best match for you
那当然是跟你最搭了
She cooks and you cook
她做饭 你也做饭
She likes mom, and so do you
她喜欢妈妈 你也喜欢
The most important thing is
最重要的是
Her mother likes you, too
她妈妈也喜欢你呀
This is a good match
这样才是良配嘛
I have a plan
我有一个计划
Hello Zhao Zong
喂 赵总
In the next round of financing,
下一轮融资的话
This side of the marketing department
市场部这边
What's the action
有什么动作
Push sales
推推销量吗
Yes
是
I'm working on a plan during this time
这段时间在做方案
After having a clear direction,
有明确的方向以后
Report to you in time
及时向您汇报
Row
行
Good
好
See you later
再见
Is Mr. Wang free to talk
王总 有空聊两句吗
These data
这些数据
Be sure to calculate many times
一定要多次核算
There can be no problems
不能出现任何的问题
Good
好
And these
还有这些
Mr. Wang
王总
This is the plan
方案就按这个做
Give it to me tomorrow
明天交给我
No problem
没问题
Mr. Wang
王总
When is the marketing department meeting
市场部什么时候开会
Call me with you
叫上我一起
Some investors want to know about it
有投资人想了解一下
A plan for promotion
推广的计划
I'll sit in
我旁听一下
To report to them
好跟他们汇报
Why should Mr. Su return it
苏总何必还把
Investors move out
投资人搬出来啊
When would you like the meeting
想什么时候开会
Just let me know
您通知就行
Mr. Wang, you are welcome
王总您客气了
I'll just be there
我列席就好
The business of our marketing department
我们市场部的业务
It is also in your charge of the vice president
也归副总裁您管
How can you just attend
怎么能只列席呢
Then later
那稍后
I'll check the time with you again
我再跟您对时间
I told you about the contract before
之前跟你说合同的问题
Are you done with it
你处理完了没有
Processing
正在处理
As soon as possible
尽快
In particular Article 6
特别是第六条
Absolutely not according to
绝对不能按照
They write like this
他们写的这样来
In that case
这样的话
It's too risky for us
对我们来说风险太大
Right
对
You'll talk to the lawyer then
你到时候跟律师
Have a good communication
好好沟通一下
Choose a compromise
选择一个折中的方法
Deal with it as soon as possible
尽快处理
It will be over next week
下个礼拜就过会了
What's the matter
怎么了
You didn't tell Wang Yi
你没有跟王奕说
Am I not vice president
我不任副总吗
No
没啊
Why
为什么
What about your ability
以你的能力呢
Be the vice president of the company
做公司这个副总
There is no problem at all
一点问题都没有
Besides
况且
You deserve it, too
你也值得
Have a better career development
拥有更好的职业发展
In this way
这样一来
We have more time
我们还有更多的时间
Can be together
可以在一起
Isn't it good
不好吗
What about my mother
那我妈妈呢
I'll work with you. Who will work with her
我陪你工作 谁陪她
It's not that I won't let you accompany my mother
我不是不让你陪妈妈
I just think
我只是觉得
Colan
可岚
What was the focus of your life before
你以前的生活重心呢
It's always been around your mother
一直都是围绕着你妈
What about yourself
对自己呢
Don't care at all
一点都不在意
There is no plan
也没有规划
I really think
我是真心觉得
You can now
你现在可以
Think more about yourself
多考虑考虑自己
Think more about your own development
多为自己的发展想一想
After all
毕竟
Mom can't stay with you all her life
妈妈不能陪你一辈子啊
What do you mean, mom
什么叫妈妈
Can't accompany me all my life
不能陪我一辈子啊
I'll go upstairs first
我先上楼了
Thank you, Jin Dao
谢谢你啊 金导
Auntie, you're welcome
阿姨 您别客气
Pay more attention to rest at ordinary times
平时还要多注意休息的
OK
好的
Jin Dao, why are you here
金导 你怎么来了
As long as the hoe dances well
只要锄头舞得好
I'm not afraid I can't dig in the corner
不怕墙角挖不到
Go to Colan's house
去可岚家
Won't that bother her
那 不会给她添麻烦吗
She is so busy with her work
她工作那么忙
Many people take care of their mothers
多个人照顾妈妈
Have a chat
聊聊天
Is she in no hurry to thank you
她感谢还来不急呢
If you feel embarrassed,
你要是觉得尴尬的话
I can wait downstairs at her house
我可以去她家楼下等着
When she comes back,
等她回来了
I'll help you hold her off
我就帮你拖住她
Send you WeChat and you will run
给你发微信 你就跑
Last time Jin Dao knew I loved fish
上次金导知道我爱吃鱼
Brought some fish
带了点鱼过来
Thank you.
谢谢你啊
No
没有
Auntie Kelan
阿姨 可岚
I'll leave you alone
我就不打扰你们了
I have to go
我先走了
Jin Dao
金导
Thank you for helping all the time, Colan
谢谢你一直帮忙可岚
Find some time
找些时间
Me and Colan
我和可岚
Please have a good meal
请你好好吃顿饭
Good
好
Kelan sends gold guide
可岚 送送金导
No need
不用了
I'll just go by myself
我自己走就行了
Goodbye, aunt
阿姨再见
Walk slowly
慢走啊
Why don't you be sensible
怎么不懂事啊
Do you want me to go upstairs
需要我上楼吗
Nothing, no need
没事 不用
You go back first
你先回吧
Don't wait for me
不用等我
Don't care too much about what you said just now
刚才的话 你别太在意
It's good for me to have dinner with my mother
我陪妈妈吃饭就好
I'll come to your house after dinner
吃完饭我来你家
How to please your mother-in-law
如何讨好丈母娘
Yu Zong, go up
余总 你上去啊
Go up and see Xiuluo Yard
上去看修罗场呀
How exciting
多刺激呀
Why are you back
怎么回来了
What are you doing down here so soon
这么快下来干嘛呀
Colan came back
可岚回来
Why didn't you tell me
你为什么不告诉我
I didn't see it when I was distracted
走神 没看到啊
Where's my cell phone
我手机呢
Hurry up and look for it
你赶紧上去找啊
Have a meal before you go
吃个饭再走
Don't live up to my great arrangement
别辜负我的大好安排
Arrangement
安排
What arrangements
什么安排
I'm trying to help you
我这不是想帮你嘛
So when Colan came back
所以可岚回来的时候
You deliberately didn't tell me
你就故意不告诉我
I said, how can you be a man
我说你这人怎么
Su Kelan
苏可岚
Go, go, go, go
快去 快去 快去
Colan
可岚
Jin Dao
金导
You don't have your cell phone
你手机没拿
To
给
Thank you
谢谢啊
It's my turn to thank you
该我谢谢您
I'm sorry
不好意思啊
Then suddenly say resign
那么突然说辞职
I'm giving you trouble
给您添麻烦了
No trouble
不麻烦
How are you doing
你 最近怎么样
It's quite good
挺好的
Just a little busy
就是有点忙
What about you
你呢
I'm just busy with the show
我就忙节目的事呗
Colan
可岚
The next time the program is docked,
下次节目对接的时候
Can it still be you
能不能还是你啊
Peng Xiao said to dock with you
彭霄说跟你对接
Compare habits
比较习惯
Han Meng has
韩梦已经
I came back from my wedding leave
休完婚假回来了
She's very nice
她人很好的
It's no problem to dock with her
跟她对接没问题
That
那
Then the next time you record the program,
那下次录节目的时候
Can you come along
你能不能一起来
In case Yu Hao is a demon again
万一余昊再作妖的话
Only you can hold him down
只有你能压得住他
Can't
不能
My mother is in the hospital today
我妈今天在医院
I forgot my medicine
药忘记拿了
Jin Dao helped to send it back
金导帮忙给送了回来
He forgot his cell phone
他手机忘了拿
I'll take it off for him
我帮他拿下来
Understand
了解
That's really troublesome to you, Jin Dao
那还真是麻烦你了金导
I made a special trip
特意跑一趟的
Sue's mother is Colan
苏妈妈是可岚
The most important person
最重要的人
Of course I have to make a special trip
我当然要特意跑一趟
Unlike you
不像你
What do you think of only yourself
什么事只想自己
Jin Dao
金导
Thank you so much today
今天真的谢谢你
Some other day my mom and I
改天我和我妈
Invite you to dinner together
一起请你吃饭
Then let's go first
那我们先走了
Let's go
走吧
Sure
好啊
Goodbye, Jin Dao
再见啊 金导
Upper
上
Follow up
跟上去啊
Head-on confrontation
正面对决
Yu Hao eats with Su's mother
余昊跟苏妈妈一起吃饭
It must be awkward
肯定特尴尬
You definitely win this round
本轮你绝对胜出
Diamond
张碧
You're all bored
你无不无聊
I made myself so boring
我把自己搞这么无聊
It's not for your happiness
还不是为了你的幸福
And I'm to blame
还怪我
You're talking like you're
你说的你好像
Don't want to poach
不想挖墙脚一样
Open the door
开门
Jin Xuan
金宣
Asshole
混蛋
Let's eat
吃饭吧
I'll do it
我来
Nothing
没事
Sit down
坐
Mom eats
妈 吃饭
Don't mention it
别客气啊
They are all home-cooked dishes
都是一些家常菜
Come
来
Aunt
阿姨
Mom eats meat
妈 吃肉
Mom has soup
妈 喝汤
The soup is delicious
汤 好喝
Drink more if it tastes good
好喝你就多喝点
Mom
妈
Aunt
阿姨
Is this tofu
这是豆腐吧
It's tofu
是豆腐
I said it looked like
我说看着像
I didn't expect you to be so bad at chatting
没想到你这么不会聊天
There is really no Jin Xuan to talk about
那确实没金宣会聊
When are you going to
你打算什么时候
Invite them to dinner at home
请他们来家里吃饭
Be angry
生气啦
No
没有
Be jealous
吃醋啦
Not bad
还好
All right
好啦
I'll teach you to chat
我教你聊天啊
Next program
下期节目
What are you going to cook
你准备做什么菜
Go back to my house
回头上我家
I taught you how to do it with my mother
我和我妈一起教你做
Good or not
好不好
Next program
下期节目
Not going
不去了
Well done
做得好好的
Why don't you go
为什么不去了
Don't know what to say
不知道说什么
Nothing
没事
I'll draw up the copy for you
文案我帮你拟
Don't you help me draw up
你可别帮我拟
I don't want that Jin Xuan
我不想让那个金宣
Another chance to haunt you
再有机会缠着你
Talk about work well
好好地聊工作
How did you become a love brain
怎么变恋爱脑了
Colan
可岚
Seriously
说真的
I'm not saying
我倒不是说
Don't want to be in your life
不想融入你的生活
It's just
只是
I may really need it
我可能真的还需要
A little time to get used to it
一点时间去适应
I can see it
看出来了
Nothing
没事
Two people together anyway
反正两个人在一起
Always learn to accommodate each other
总要学着互相迁就嘛
Then we
那我们
Just slowly try to find the rhythm
就慢慢试着找节奏
Don't stop because
不要再因为
Who accommodates whose problems
谁迁就谁的问题
And angry
而怄气了
Good or not
好不好
That's not true
这话不对啊
Why is it wrong
怎么不对啊
You were the first to be angry today
今天是你先怄气的
Don't forget
别忘了
All right
好吧
That
那
Who will be punished in the future
以后谁怄气罚谁
How to punish
怎么罚
Then
那就
Give each other a kiss
让对方亲一口
Is there enough penalty
罚够了吗
No
没有
Divorce
离婚
What's the situation, sister
什么情况啊 大姐
Earnest
认真的
How to go for a tour
怎么去旅个游
I got divorced when I came back.
回来就离婚了呢
What the hell have you done
你到底干了什么呀
How do you do
您好
Please help me maintain it
麻烦帮我保养一下
All right, this way, please
好嘞 这边请
Wife
老婆
I'm not happy to go home
回家了 不高兴啊
Haven't had enough fun
没玩够
Forgot a bunch of things
忘带一堆东西
And lost
还迷路了
Do you dare to be more reliable
你敢不敢更靠谱一点
But look at that
但你看啊
If it weren't for
要不是因为
We're cornered
我们走投无路
Get stuck on the road
被卡在路上
How can you meet herders
又怎么会碰到牧民
Start a period with them
跟他们开启一段
True free travel
真正的自由行
This kind of relationship with local people
这种跟当地人
Surprise journey of living together
一起生活的惊喜旅程
Is it better than making a plan
是不是比制定计划
More interesting
更有趣
I also got it made by hand
还得了人家手工做的
A polished bracelet
开过光的镯子
Isn't it beautiful
多漂亮 是不是
As good-looking as you
跟你一样好看
Where's your ring
你戒指呢
You're not
你不是
Have long taken a fancy to others
早就看上人家
Is this bracelet gone
这镯子了嘛
When people started,
人家一开始
I didn't want to give it
不是不想给嘛
The night before I came back
我回来前一天晚上
Drinking with others
跟人家喝酒
People agreed to change it
人家才同意换的
Don't worry
你别急啊
I was going to
我本来打算的
At dawn tomorrow
明天天一亮
Just buy a new ring
就重新去买个戒指
Make sure it's exactly the same as before
保证跟之前的一模一样
Mengmeng
梦梦
That's why you're getting a divorce
就为这事你就要离婚啊
You still laugh at me
你还笑我
Can you send a circle of friends
能不能发个朋友圈
Laugh
笑
You can still laugh
你还笑的出来啊
What happened between you and Sucron
你和苏可岚那会
How can I help you
我怎么帮你的
Now your uncle and I are divorced
现在你舅舅我离婚了
You're laughing right here
你就在这笑
She said leave
她说离
If you don't agree, it's over
你不同意不就完了
Then get married
那结婚
It's a matter for two people
是两个人的事
I also have a good temper
我也有脾气的好嘛
I coaxed and comforted all the way
我一路哄 一路安慰
She's getting too far
她越来越过分
Leave just leave
离就离呗
Who is afraid of who
谁怕谁啊
According to your temper
按照你的脾气
I guess it won't be a few days
我估计没几天
You will go on your knees and beg for a remarriage
你就会去跪求复婚了
You two haven't had a few days
你俩没几天
I'm sure I'll get my license again
肯定又会重新领证了
Absolutely impossible
绝对不可能
How can you put a wedding ring
怎么能把结婚戒指
What about replacing this kind of thing
这种东西给换掉呢
I really have a crush on it
我是真心看上
Do you have that broken bracelet
那个破手镯了吗
I can't believe he traded his wedding ring for it
他居然拿结婚戒指去换
It's just a ring
不就一个戒指吗
Buy an identical one
买个一模一样的
It would be nice if you didn't
不就好了
This
这
This is telling me about divorce
这竟然就跟我说离婚
Do you know what angry words are
你知道什么是气话吗
As soon as I talk about divorce,
我一说离婚
He was unequivocal
他竟然毫不含糊
I agreed
就答应了
How did he put his wedding ring
他怎么把结婚戒指
It's changed
给换了呢
Colan
可岚
Mom
妈
How's Mengmeng
梦梦怎么样啦
Fell asleep
睡着了
She didn't put the divorce
她没把离婚的事
Tell her parents
跟她爸妈说
Should still want to get back together
应该还是想复合的吧
You are now
你现在
Are you going to discuss with Yu Hao
是去找余昊商量吗
Then after you
那你以后
I also plan to run at both ends all the time
也打算一直两头跑啊
After you
你以后
That's what I'm going to do
就打算这样
Have you been running at both ends
一直两头跑吗
You are in this state
你这种状态
Will he be dissatisfied
他会不会不满意啊
If he dares to be dissatisfied
他要是敢不满意
Then I don't want him
那我就不要他了
All right
行吧
What happens in the marketing department in the future
以后市场部的事
Go straight to Su Zong
直接找苏总
Why are you in the office again
怎么又来办公室了
Is this home occupied by Gong Wenxing
这不家被龚文星占了嘛
I think they are just angry
我觉得他俩就是怄气
Mengmeng didn't take the divorce
梦梦没把离婚那事
Tell his parents
和他爸妈说
Gong Wenxing's end
龚文星那头
Didn't you tell his mother either
是不是也没和他妈妈说
That
那
Make an appointment
约个时间
Let them talk
让他俩聊聊呗
I feel like meeting
我觉得见了面
Let's talk
说开了
It should be all right
应该就没事了
Good
好呀
Is there anything else you can do
那你还有什么事吗
If it's all right, I'll just
要是没什么事的话我就
Go home
回家了
Your mother
你妈妈
Are you unhappy?
是不是不高兴了呀
My mother
我妈
Your mother must be upset
你妈肯定是不高兴了
Your reflex arc is too long
你反射弧也太长了吧
Now I think of my mother
现在才想起我妈
But I really didn't expect it
不过我是真的没想到啊
You can chat like this
你聊天会这么尬
Chatting days should be
闲聊天究竟应该
What are you talking about
聊些什么呢
Chatting at home
唠家常呗
Were you at home before
难道你以前在家
Don't talk about it
不聊这些
I'm sorry
对不起啊
When my mother was still here,
我妈还在的时候
It's all about my dad's job
聊的都是我爸的工作
And then my mom left
后来我妈走了
Grandma always felt that
外婆一直觉得
It's my dad's responsibility
是我爸的责任
I won't let him see me
也就不让他见我了
From that time on
从那个时候开始
I've been talking to Gong Wenxing
我就一直跟龚文星
Live with Grandma
和外婆一起住
Maybe because at that time
可能因为那个时候
Young
年纪小
Don't dare to speak
不太敢说话
I'm also afraid of saying the wrong thing
也怕说错话
You said in case I said something wrong
你说万一我说错话
Make them unhappy
弄得他们不高兴
How embarrassed I am
我多尴尬
Maybe it's because of this
可能是因为这个
That led me to now
才导致我现在
Not very good at chatting, are you
不太会聊天吧
So you
那你
Since then
从那之后
Haven't seen your dad since
就再也没见过你爸了吗
In the first grade of junior high school
初中一年级的时候
At the school gate
在校门口
He came to me
他找过我
It was my birthday
那天我生日
He gave me a pair of shoes
他送了我双鞋
But my grandmother lost it
但被我外婆给丢了
Since then
从那之后
I haven't seen it before
就没见过
So you hate your dad
那你讨厌你爸
Think it's because of him
觉得是因为他
Your mother just
你妈妈才
It can't be said to be annoying
也说不上讨厌
Then why don't you see him
那你为什么不见他
See him
见他
Don't know what to say
不知道说什么
You can't talk
你不会聊天
Afraid of embarrassment
怕尴尬
And I'll hold you
我还要拉着你
Have dinner with my mother
和我妈一起吃饭
Nothing
没事
I learn slowly
我慢慢学
I was so embarrassed at the dinner table just now
刚饭桌上那么尴尬
Aren't you full
你是不是没吃饱啊
Then I'll make you something delicious
那我给你做点好吃的
Good or not
好不好
Thank you
谢谢
Sweet
甜的
Why is it sweet
为什么是甜的
It's sweet
就是甜的
You haven't eaten anything sweet
你没吃过甜的
Bean curd should not be salty
豆腐脑不应该是咸的
Or is it spicy
或者是辣的吗
And spicy
还放辣
This Chongqing people eat spicy food
这重庆人吃辣
Isn't that normal
不很正常吗
Then you can't put everything spicy, can you
那也不能什么都放辣吧
Do you eat a brown sugar cake
难道吃个红糖糍粑
You put it spicy, too
你也放辣
There is some point in saying it
说的有点道理
Bean curd, it's not a sweet
豆腐脑它又不是甜食
But there is sweet bean curd
可就是有甜的豆腐脑啊
I don't want to blame you
不是我说你
Make food software
做美食软件的
Why are you so ignorant
怎么那么孤陋寡闻
Knowing and accepting are two different things
知道和接受是两码事
Don't you think
你就不觉得
What we just talked about
刚刚我们聊的
Especially without nutrition
特别没营养
But is it interesting
但挺有意思吗
How interesting
哪有意思啊
My dad used to tell me
以前我爸和我说过
Food is opening the conversation
食物是打开话题
The best way
最好的方式
He said that no matter the north or south,
他说不论南北方的
How big is the dietary difference
饮食差异有多大
Everyone greets each other
大家相互问候的
The ways are
方式都是
Did you eat
你吃了吗
There is culture in food
食物里蕴涵着文化
Personality
个性
And growing up experience and so on
还有成长经历等等
Is to know a person
是了解一个人
The best opportunity
最好的契机
When you are curious and concerned,
当你好奇关心的时候
It's not that hard to chat
闲聊天其实没那么难
Sweet bean curd
甜豆腐脑
Is it delicious
好吃吗
It's still a little weird
还是有点怪怪的
Be full
吃饱了
Stay and work overtime tonight
今天晚上留下来加班
You
你
Don't you think
就不觉得
If someone suddenly comes to work overtime,
如果有人突然来加班
No one will come
不会有人来
He can't get in when he comes
来了他也进不来
I turned off the electronic lock
我把电子锁关了
Work overtime
加班吧
Don't
不要
To
要
Hello
喂
Zhao Zong
赵总
Yu Hao
余昊
Zhao Zong said next week
赵总说下周
I'm going to come over
要过来一趟
Work overtime
加班吧
The cell phone rang
手机响了
Don't you answer the phone when you work overtime
加班不接电话的吗
Mr. Han came back from his honeymoon
韩总 度蜜月回来了
Yeah
是啊
Dark circles are so heavy
黑眼圈这么重
Work pressure has been so great recently
最近工作压力有这么大
He
他呀
I went back to the company to pick up the documents last night
昨天晚上回公司取文件
I don't know what happened
也不知道怎么搞的
Locked in the company
被锁在公司了
Don't say last night
你可别说昨晚了
What happened
什么情况
My one
我那个
Last night
昨天晚上
Work overtime in the office
在办公室加班
I don't know why
不知道咋的
I was locked in my office
就被锁在办公室了
It's rare for Yu to say
难得余总说
No overtime tonight
今天晚上不用加班
What are you doing back at the company
你又回去公司干什么呀
I still have something to finish here
我这还有东西没做完呢
I'm afraid I'll be scolded tomorrow if I can't finish it.
做不完怕明天被骂啊
Good
好好
See you later
再见
All right
好嘞
I don't know how to put it
不知道咋说呢
You last night
你昨天晚上
It's really locked in the company
真的被锁在公司啦
Where did my medlar go
那个 我那枸杞去哪了呢
Yu Zong
余总
Colan didn't come home last night either
昨天晚上可岚也没回家
I remember your family
我记得你们家
Is it also occupied by someone
是不是也被人占了
Yao Qian
姚茜
The theme of next week's program
下周的节目主题
You check with the program group
你和节目组对一下
Okay, Sister Kelan
好的可岚姐
Mr. Su last night
苏总 昨天晚上
I made it up
我拟好了
Details of advertising shooting
广告拍摄的细节
Do you want to check it
要不要核对一下
Check it, Mr. Su
核对一下啊 苏总
You run to the office
你跑到办公室去
He also locked the door
他还把门给锁了
You two just sit opposite each other
你俩就对坐着
Work together
一块工作啊
Really good
真行
You think you two are high school students
你当你俩是高中生
I'm studying for the college entrance examination here
在这复习高考呢
I worked all night and looked at my cell phone
工作一晚上了还看手机
A moment in spring night
春宵一刻啊
It was wasted by you like this
就被你这么给浪费了
Or say
还是说
You hate the office
你嫌办公室
I can't let go of my hands and feet
放不开手脚呀
What are you talking about?
说什么呢你
The one from the technical department
技术部那个
Interns with black-rimmed glasses
带黑框眼镜的实习生
You know, right
知道吧
People also spent the night yesterday
人家昨天也一晚上
It's in the office
在办公室呢
Say it or not
说不说
There are witnesses
有证人呢
Are you two really apart from work
你俩真的除了工作
Didn't do anything
啥也没干
It's not dry at all
一点都没干
It didn't dry at all
一丁点儿都没干
Honestly confess
老实交代
Hurry up, hurry up
快点快点
Mr. Sue, I'm free now
苏总 我现在有空
I reported to you about the marketing department
和您汇报市场部的事了
Is Sue always listening
苏总在听吗
Su Zong
苏总
Give me ten minutes
等我十分钟
Is it convenient
要不方便
Then let's take another time
那我们就改天吧
Good
好
No problem
没问题
I'm listening
我在听着
Good
好
Su Zong
苏总
Just a moment, please
您稍等一下啊
Sure
行啊
Then you tell me first
那你先跟我说吧
What adjustments are there
有什么调整
I'll let Yao Qian
到时候我让姚茜
Follow-up
跟进
Yao Qian, communicate directly
姚茜直接沟通吧
Row
行
That's it
这样啊
How many people come altogether
总共来几个人
When will the plan come out
方案什么时候出来呢
Good
好
Are there any questions
还有什么问题吗
This is right
这个是对的
Yes
是
Right, right, right
对对对
All right
行 那
You have a problem
您有问题
Call me anytime
随时给我打电话
The contract amount is all wrong
合同金额都是错的
Why did you send it to me?
怎么发我这里来了
Can you pour me a cup of coffee
你帮我倒杯咖啡吧
Su Kelan, you are really good
苏可岚 你可真行
I brought my wash bag with me
洗漱包都带了
You don't do anything
你啥也不干
Keep your voice down
小声一点
Really
真是
Coming, coming
来了 来了
Quickly
快
Get off work early today
今天早点下班
Eat dinner with your mother
陪你妈吃完晚饭
Come to my house
来我家
What are you doing
干嘛呀
Quick back
快回
Look at it. Come on, come on
看看 快点快点
Let me give it to you again
又让我给你
Make coffee as an assistant
当助理泡咖啡啊
It's awkward
闹别扭了
Didn't you start the meeting
那不是你先开会的吗
You still blame somebody else
你还怪人家
Then I drove it for him, too
那我也是为了他开的
Let me be promoted to vice president for no reason
莫名其妙让我升副总
Make Lao Wang unhappy
弄得老王不爽
Just deliberately pick the time
才故意挑时间
Call me in the middle of the night
半夜打电话给我
If I don't answer it,
我要是不接
He's even more upset with me
他更看我不爽了
Then you take the attitude of vice president
那你就以副总的姿态
Let him accommodate your work
让他迁就你工作
I didn't promise Yu Hao to be the vice president
我没答应余昊要当副总
Ah
啊
That's what bothers you
你就为这事烦啊
I still think what happened
我还以为什么事呢
So most of these people
那这大部分人
Everyone wants a promotion and a raise
都希望升职加薪
You're the only one here
就你在这腻歪
And Versailles with me
跟我凡尔赛呢
No
不是
The situation of my family, you
我家的情况你
It's not like you don't know
你又不是不知道
He is not in the company now to correct it.
他现在也不在公司纠正
Talk to him again
再和他说
I guess he will be unhappy again
估计他又要不开心
I think
我觉得
It's normal for him to be unhappy
他不开心才是正常的呀
It means he cares about you
说明他在意你啊
Look at that
你看啊
What about most men
大部分的男人呢
I can't wait for my wife
都巴不得老婆
What about staying at home full time
全职在家呢
He gave you a promotion
他让你升职
One is hope
一是希望
Have more time
有更多的时间
To be with you
能跟你待在一起
More importantly,
更重要的是
Show that he trusts you
表明他信任你
Recognize you
认可你
I know
我知道
But my mother
可是我妈
Colan
可岚
This may come to say
这话可能说来
It doesn't sound very nice
不太好听啊
But think about it carefully
但你仔细想想啊
In your longest future life
在你未来最长的人生里
Can accompany you to the end
能陪你走到最后的
That man
那个人
Who is it
是谁
Ever since your family
自从你们家
What about after what happened
出了那件事以后呢
Whether it's love or life,
不管是恋爱还是生活
You've been around all the time
你都一直在围着
Your mother turns
你妈妈转
Completely without yourself
完全没有了你自己
What about this matter
这件事情呢
Yu Hao didn't discuss with you
余昊没有跟你商量
That's really what he did wrong
那确实是他做的不对
But if you think about it,
但你仔细想想
This job
这份工作
For yourself,
对你本身而言
What's more important is that
更重要的不就是
What is its value and significance
它的价值跟意义吗
Mengmeng
梦梦
Don't forget to make an appointment today
别忘了今天约好了
Have dinner together
一起吃饭
I also plan to make a fuss
还打算闹情绪
Stay at my house for a few days
在我家住几天啊
I think I'm taking up your time
嫌我占用你时间啦
Change the subject
转移话题
Can you solve the problem
就能解决问题了吗
Aren't you changing the subject, too
你不也在转移话题吗
No matter, no matter
不管了 不管了
Anyway, I'm tired of looking at him now
反正我现在看他就烦
It is impossible for me to take the initiative to find him
我是不可能主动找他的
The most boring thing about people is to be angry
人最没意思的就是怄气
You also think I said divorce
你也觉得我说离婚
Just angry
只是怄气
Then let me ask you something
那我问你
If it were you
如果是你
You will take the wedding ring
你会拿婚戒
Go get another one
去换一个
Something that doesn't matter
无关紧要的东西吗
He brought me a wedding ring
他给我带上婚戒
The moment you look at me
望向我的那一刻
I seem to see his future
我仿佛看到了他未来
A life entrusted to me
托付给我的一生
And I put the ring on
而我把戒指戴在
When he has it,
他手上的时候
The same
同样的
I put all my promises
我把所有的承诺
And live up to
和不辜负
It all turns into this
都化作这
A small ring
一枚小小的戒指
Always stay at his fingertips
永远陪在他指尖
But what about him
可是他呢
He not only casually
他不仅随随便便
Just replace it
就把它换掉
Even why am I unhappy
甚至连我为什么不高兴
He doesn't even know
他都不知道
I'm sad
我伤心的
It was he who took my sadness
是他把我的伤心
As a joke
当作玩闹
You didn't come back all night yesterday
昨天你一宿没回来
This will be my lodging fee
这就当我的借宿费了
Uncle wishes you to make persistent efforts
舅舅祝你再接再厉
Bravely create brilliant achievements
勇创辉煌
Han Meng is downstairs now
韩梦现在就在楼下
She talks to Su Kelan every day
她每天都会和苏可岚
Go downstairs for coffee
下楼喝咖啡
Who said I was looking for her
谁说我是来找她的呀
It's not that you apologize if you want to
不是 你想道歉就道歉
Coax if you want
想哄就哄
Can you leave me alone in my work
能不能别来打扰我工作
It still depends on my family
还赖我家
Take up my personal space
占用我的个人空间
Big Brother
大哥
Call Uncle
叫舅舅
I used to live under the same roof
以前同住一个屋檐下
I didn't see you. You're not used to it
也没看你不习惯啊
Why not now
现在怎么就不行了
I understand you
我懂你
Home is so boring
家里太没意思了
How exciting the office is
办公室多带劲
Is there something wrong with it
是不是有毛病啊
Are you idle and have nothing to do
是不是闲得没事干
How do you talk to your uncle
怎么跟你舅舅说话呢
Give me back
还我
Don't don't
不要不要
Haohao, why are you like this
昊昊 你怎么这样
I'm telling you
我给你说
You gotta go, gotta go
你赶紧走赶紧走
Go quickly
赶紧走
If you don't leave, I'll call security
再不走我叫保安了
You said
你说
I changed my wedding ring
我换了婚戒
Is it too much
很过分吗
Then you should ask her
那你应该问她
Why are you asking me
你问我干嘛啊
You are more reasonable
你比较讲道理
When did feelings make sense
感情什么时候讲过道理
Besides
况且
Even if it's reasonable
即便是讲道理
This wedding ring is for the two of you
这个婚戒是你们两个人
Jointly owned
共同拥有的
You shouldn't be presumptuous
你就不应该擅作主张
Go home early at night
晚上早点回家
I'll have dinner together
我来一起吃饭
I can tell you what
我可告诉你啊
If you don't leave,
你要再不走
Han Meng will come back to work soon
韩梦马上就回来上班了
It's not like I didn't apologize
我又不是没道歉
No mistake
没认错
Not coaxed
没哄
It's just a ring
一个戒指而已
Doesn't anyone matter yet
还没有人重要吗
Always talk about divorce
动不动就说离婚
It's her fault, isn't it
是她不对吧
So
所以
It was I who made trouble without reason
是我无理取闹
You've been putting up with me
你一直在忍我
You're innocent
你一身无辜
Enough now, right
现在忍够了是吧
Mengmeng
梦梦
You don't even care
你都不在意
What am I keeping it for
我还留着干什么
Mengmeng
梦梦
Su Zong
苏总
Mr. Li of CICC will arrive soon
中金的李总马上到了
Mr. Li
李总
I will confirm the law firm in the near future
近期我会确认律所
And accounting firm
和会计事务所
What are the compliance risks
有什么合规的风险
Avoid in advance first
先提前规避
It's very thoughtful
想得很周到嘛
That's right
对了
Are you guys
你们是不是
Promotion in the next stage
下个阶段的推广
To sign Diamond's endorsement
要签张碧的代言
Diamond endorsement
张碧代言
Yeah
对啊
Lao Wang's side is not
老王那边不是
Has been with Diamond Brokerage Company
已经跟张碧经纪公司
Are we talking
在谈了吗
And Diamond's company
和张碧的公司
Have you communicated yet
沟通过了吗
It has been settled
已经谈妥了
Did the other party mention anything
对方有没有提什么
Mr. Wang
王总
Excuse me for interrupting
不好意思 打扰一下
Is it convenient for Mr. Wang to have a word
王总方便借一步说话吗
One thing
有件事
I need to confirm with you
我需要和您确认一下
Su Zong
苏总
If it's a work thing,
如果是工作上的事
Say it right here
就在这说吧
Are you going to let Diamond speak for you
您是准备让张碧代言吗
This thing, ah
这件事儿啊
That's right
没错
We have talked with the other company
我们已经和对方公司
It's been communicated
沟通过了
What are you dissatisfied with
您有什么不满意的
Place
地方吗
The company introduced a new spokesperson
公司推出新的代言人
No problem
没问题
But Diamond
但张碧
And "what to eat next"
和“下顿吃什么”的
Inconsistency of endorsement tonality
代言调性不符
Look at me
你看我
Forget this crop
忘了这茬了
Colan
可岚
You're Mr. Yu's girlfriend
你是余总的女朋友
I must mind in my heart
心里肯定介意
But taking a private position
但是把私人立场
And emotions to work
和情绪带到工作当中来
Will seriously affect the judgment of work
会严重影响工作的判断
What do you say
你说呢
Mr. Wang
王总
Potential buyers of the company
公司的潜在购买群体
Mainly female
以女性为主
Have you ever thought about
你有想过
They have Diamond
张碧在她们那里的
Acceptance
接受度吗
When the time comes, if they are not satisfied,
到时候如果她们不满意
What to do
怎么办
Will it affect the sales volume
会不会影响销量
This matter
这件事
I hope you can give up as soon as possible
我希望你能尽早放弃
For the sake of safeguarding the interests of the company
出于维护公司利益
My side will not agree
我这边是不会同意的
Is it Diamond's contract
是不是张碧的合同
It's already here with you
已经到你这了
Hold it for me first
先帮我卡着
Thank you
谢谢
Heard
听说
Mr. Wang is face to face
王总当面
Was killed by Su Kelan
被苏可岚给怼了
Have you heard about it
你们听说了吗
Mr. Wang asked Diamond to speak for him
王总让张碧代言
Is it true or not
真的假的
So exciting
这么刺激
No wonder Sister Kelan just now
怪不得可岚姐刚才
Went to the marketing department
去市场部了
You don't know
你们可不知道
Just now, Sister Kelan can talk directly
刚刚可岚姐可直接放话
I won't pass this plan
这个方案我不会通过
But Sister Lan still has this
可岚姐还有这么
The tough side
强硬的一面
Who can bear this
这搁谁能忍啊
If my husband is like this,
要是我老公这样
I can't possibly agree
我也不可能同意啊
If I were you
要是我啊
Just report to Mr. Yu directly
直接就跟余总打报告了
Do you still need to tear it off by yourself
还用得着自己下场撕吗
You said Diamond spoke for me
你们说张碧代言
Is it Yu Zong's meaning
是不是余总的意思
It's not that you guys are talking nonsense
不是 你们瞎说什么呢
Proceed from the interests of the company
从公司利益出发
Diamond endorsement is really inappropriate
张碧代言确实不合适
I think Sister Colan
我觉得可岚姐
It makes sense
说的有道理
If this thing
如果这件事
She asked Yu Zong to come forward to solve it
她让余总出面解决
It will only make people think that it is
只会让人认为是
Sister Ke Lan has a problem with her ability to work
可岚姐工作能力有问题
Even at this time
就算这个时候
Yu always came out against it
余总出来反对
It also makes people think that
也会让人认为
It's Sister Kelan who blows the wind
是可岚姐吹的风
I don't know anything day by day
什么都不懂 一天天的
Have lunch together later
等会儿一起吃午饭
No, I'm worried about Mengmeng
不用了 我担心梦梦
I'll go find her
我去找一下她
Maybe I have to accompany her today
可能今天还得陪她
Yu Zongsu is always busy
余总 苏总比较忙
Some replies may be slow
有些回复可能比较慢
It will affect the work of the marketing department
会影响市场部工作
Can Mr. Yu give a personal reply
余总能否亲自批复一下
Is Wang Yi embarrassing you
王奕是不是为难你了
Yu Zong
余总
There is a problem with the technology
技术那边有问题
Do you have time to have a meeting together
有没有空一起开个会
Good
好
Where are you? Are you all right
你在哪儿 没事吧
Hello Yao Qian
喂 姚茜
Hello, Sister Colan
喂 可岚姐
No, it's bad. Something happened
不好了出事了
About Diamond's endorsement
张碧代言的事
It was leaked out
被泄漏出去了
I told you to leave me alone
跟你说了别再烦我
Yu Zong, look at me like this
余总 你看我这身
Which is more suitable for endorsement
哪个更适合代言呀
What if he says he likes it all
他要说都喜欢怎么办
What for
干嘛
I'm busy. Don't bother me
忙着呢 你别烦我
Sister, you didn't look at your cell phone
姐 你没看手机
Then don't look
那就别看了
Hello
喂
I heard it was Diamond
听说是张碧那边
Always wanted to speak for "what to eat"
一直想给“吃什么”代言
Then she is not suitable
那她不合适吧
Image temperament is a long story
形象 气质一言难尽
Really inappropriate
确实不合适
Yao Qian
姚茜
Didn't you agree with Diamond's endorsement
不是没同意张碧代言吗
How did it get out
怎么就传出去了
It must be the news from Mr. Wang
肯定是王总透的消息
Want to push Diamond
想推动张碧
Put pressure on Sister Colan
给可岚姐施压
Do you think he is stupid
你说他是不是傻啊
Hello Sister Meng
喂 梦姐
Something happened
出事了
Mr. Wang
王总
Really don't let advertising companies
真的还不让广告公司
Change the scheme
更改方案吗
Sue always said she wouldn't
苏总说她是不会
Agreed to let Diamond speak for him
同意让张碧代言的
Let you know the news
让你们透消息
Tell the media
给媒体那边说
Talking about endorsement
在谈代言
Is it thorough
透了吗
Thoroughly
透了
If she doesn't agree
她要是不同意啊
Let herself and Diamond
就让她自己和张碧
Explain when the bad guys go
解释当坏人去
Su Kelan's people
苏可岚的人
There must be no good
准没好事
Hello, the number you dialed
您好 您拨打的电话
You're out of your mind
你脑子进水啊
Thought to get out of this matter
以为透这事出去
The media will support you and force Su Kelan
媒体会挺你逼苏可岚
Agree to endorse
同意代言啊
Look at the present
你看看现在
Are they all talking about
是不是都在说
Diamond is not suitable
张碧不合适
What a big deal
多大点事啊
Doesn't this also increase the attention
这不也增加了关注度吗
I'll avoid it first
我先避避
Now Su Kelan
这下苏可岚
If you don't promise, you have to promise
不答应也得答应
Wang Yi Pig
王奕猪啊
Don't come in for the meeting
开会也不进来
Yao Qian
姚茜
You go straight to the marketing department to find him
你直接去市场部找他
People in the marketing department claim to be
市场部的人号称
Meeting with an advertising agency
和广告公司开会
The media calls are ringing off the hook
媒体电话都打爆了
I didn't answer any of them
我一个也没接
But if you don't reply,
但再不回复的话
It's bound to cause controversy
肯定会引发争议的
When the time comes, the reputation of the company
到时候对公司信誉
It's not good either
也不好
Clarify
澄清啊
Say there is no endorsement
说没有代言的事
Diamond Company
张碧公司那边
Let that fool go by himself
让那个傻子自己去
Clean up a mess
收拾烂摊子
Mr. Wang
王总
Look at the news in the group
你看群里消息
You don't deal with the media
你们不和媒体打交道
Don't understand
不了解
This is not the first time
这事情不第一时间
Properly handle the clarification
妥善处理澄清的话
It will lead to escalation of contradictions
会导致矛盾升级
Rival companies will also fan the flames
对手公司也会煽风点火
Say "what to eat" and leak the news
说“吃什么”泄漏消息
Have no credibility
没有信誉
Yao Qian, if now, immediately
姚茜 如果现在立刻
Clarify that Diamond was not asked to speak for him
澄清没有找张碧代言
Others will make excuses
还有人会找借口
Attack our company
攻击我们公司吗
It will be fine if it is fast
快的话就还好
And if it is clarified,
而且澄清的话
I can't find an excuse to make trouble
也找不到借口闹
But Diamond's end
不过张碧那头
It must be hard
肯定不好受
Because all this time
因为一直以来
There are brands that say she is native
就有品牌说她土
This clarification
这一澄清
Repeat one's hand
多此一举
Discuss what
商量什么
It's nothing more than saying
无非是说
Didn't speak for this matter
没代言这件事情
Say it's me
推说是我
Make your own decisions
自作主张呗
These people
这帮人
I can't wait to see my joke
都巴不得看我笑话呢
Mengmeng
梦梦
You go and find Mr. Wang later
你一会儿去找一下王总
Implement the advertising plan
落实一下广告方案
Let Diamond participate
让张碧参演
You have to agree to endorse it
你要同意代言啊
No
不是
In this way
这样
Yao Qian
姚茜
You're going to talk to the press later
你一会去和媒体
There are two more people
还有两头的人
Take air separately
分别通一下气
Just say two people have been
就说两个人一直
They are all very good friends
都是很好的朋友
So our company
所以我们公司
There is an advertisement
有一支广告
Mr. Yu invited Diamond to play in friendship
余总请张碧友情出演
The result was misinformed as an endorsement
结果误传成了代言
What's the matter? Is there a problem
怎么了 有问题吗
No
没有
In that case
这样的话
It is true that on both sides
确实对两边
There will be no more problems
都不会再有问题
But
可是
Why do you want to give Wang Yi a step down
干嘛要给王奕台阶下啊
This is his pot
这本来就是他的锅
It's all one company
都是一个公司
Divide what yours and mine
分什么你的我的
What he said
他说出去的话
On behalf of the company
就代表公司
Something happened and pushed him out
出了事把他推出去
It doesn't make people feel that
不会让人觉得
Is the management of the company chaotic
公司管理混乱吗
Sister Kelan
那可岚姐
Is it right now to communicate
是现在立刻沟通吗
Or wait for you and Diamond
还是等您和张碧
I'll talk about it after I have communicated at both ends
余总两头沟通过了再说
Don't wait
不等了
A scolded person
被骂的人
It must be hard now
现在肯定也不好受
And it took a long time
而且拖久了
If you clarify again,
再澄清的话
The credibility is also insufficient
公信力也不足
Let's do it now
现在去办吧
Good
好
Elder sister
大姐
I see you simply because
我看你根本就是因为
Look at Diamond being scolded. It's too pitiful
看张碧被人骂太可怜了
At this time
都这时候
Why are you still thinking about her
你还贴心考虑她干嘛啊
Our own infighting
我们自己内斗
Be scolded for implicating others as chips
牵连别人当筹码被骂
What's going on
算怎么回事
Then look at them
那就看他们
Shoot advertisements together
一起拍广告啊
Do you feel at ease
你放心吗
Elder sister
大姐
Someone who needs to be so defensive
需要那么防着的人
Then I don't want it
那我不要也罢
Completely defenseless
完全不防
Or the heart is too big
要不就是心太大
Or people are too nice
要么就是人太好
If you believe
如果你相信
It's because people are too nice
是因为人太好
Does the good man think
那好人会不会觉得
Your heart is too big
你心太大呢
If we say
如果说
Good people don't think you are too big-hearted
好人不觉得你心太大
Then do you think
那你会不会觉得
Good people's hearts are too big
好人心太大
What tongue twisters are you talking about
说什么绕口令呢
It's too complicated for me to understand
太复杂了 我听不懂
Just play dumb for me
你就给我装傻吧
Then the head is the way
那么头头是道
How are you
你怎么样啊
I'm I'm okay
我 我没事
Where are you
你在哪啊
Send me a location
给我发个定位
I came to see you
我来找你
Jin Dao
金导
I'm sorry
不好意思啊
There's something I'd like to ask you for
有件事我想请你帮个忙
Advertising Diamond's Role
广告张碧的角色
Deal with as friends
处理成朋友关系
Don't give any hint of a couple
别有任何情侣的暗示
Otherwise, it will definitely fry the pan
否则肯定还会炸锅
It's going to blow up again
要再炸了
We're not responsible for cleaning up the mess
我们不负责收拾烂摊子
Sorry for the subscriber you dialed
对不起您拨叫的用户
Unable to connect temporarily
暂时无法接通
Please dial again later
请您稍后再拨
Don't you bother me
你不烦我吗
Why are you bothering me
你这会烦我干嘛啊
Do you see my jokes
看我笑话吗
No
不是
I think it's appropriate, too
我也觉得合适
That's settled then
那就这么定了
Bye bye
拜拜
I'm with Mengmeng tonight
今晚我陪梦梦
OK
好的